<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-04-11T09:05:14-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Red Butte Garden</title><subtitle>The official website of Red Butte Garden</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Botanical Watercolor 2</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/botanical-watercolor-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Botanical Watercolor 2" /><published>2017-04-10T20:04:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T20:58:50-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/botanical-watercolor-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/botanical-watercolor-2/">&lt;p class=&quot;text-center red bold&quot;&gt;NOTE: NO CLASS APRIL 14&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Building on skills and concepts introduced in &lt;em&gt;Botanical Watercolor 1&lt;/em&gt;, this class will focus on realistic expression of form, structure, texture, and color using wash and dry brush watercolor techniques. Students will work from simple plant forms e.g. gourds, fruit, and leaves&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong class=&quot;green&quot;&gt;Instructor:&lt;/strong&gt; Elaine Hultgren&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong class=&quot;green&quot;&gt;Limit:&lt;/strong&gt; 15&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/refund-policy&quot;&gt;RED BUTTE GARDEN REFUND AND CANCELLATION POLICY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Materials List&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparent Watercolors&lt;/strong&gt; - Recommended Winsor Newton Artists’ grade (Not Cotman)
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Either 5 ml or 14/15 ml size:&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Winsor Lemon – (cool)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cadmium Yellow Pale –(warm) or Cadmium Yellow (warm)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Winsor Blue RS (Red Shade) – (warm) or Ultramarine Blue (warm)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Winsor Blue GS (Green Shade) - (cool)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Quinacridone Magenta – (cool) or Permanent Rose (cool)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cadmium Red – (warm)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brushes:&lt;/strong&gt; Sceptre Gold recommended for beginners and intermediates: one each – Sceptre Gold II size 2 and 5, or Kolinsky sables: Raphael 8404 Brand: size 1 and 4 or Winsor Newton Series 7 brand: size 2 and 4.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong class=&quot;green&quot;&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt; Utrecht Art Supply (in Sugarhouse) has Red Sable brushes.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optional but good:&lt;/strong&gt; “The Masters” Brush cleaner, a cake soluble with water.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Detail Brush:&lt;/strong&gt; A specialty brush you must order online BUT sometimes available at art stores. I use a Dick Blick brand: size 2 Studio Sable, Kolinsky Sable Detail. Also available: size 3 Winsor Newton Miniature Kolinsky Sable. Detail brushes have shorter hairs but are fuller at the ferrule to hold more paint. This brush used in dry brush stage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mixing Brush:&lt;/strong&gt; A #3,4,5 OLD brush you can use to mix colors with. I use a Loew- Cornell round #4 brush I purchased at Michaels craft store.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pencils:&lt;/strong&gt; 2B, HB, 2H 4H – A blue Col-erase pencil will be provided if you do not have it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracing Paper:&lt;/strong&gt; 11x14, Canson, Foundation Series, Red, White, and Black cover, AND can be bought locally only at Hobby Lobby for $8 but there is always a 40% coupon available online. This tracing paper is the most translucent of all such papers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watercolor Paper:&lt;/strong&gt; One pack 11x14 140lb Strathmore Ready Cut Hot Press (6 sheets to a pack). One pack costs $6.37 through Dick Blick online. Utrecht (in Sugarhouse) may have it stocked in store. Must be &quot;hot press.&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other:&lt;/strong&gt; Porcelain palette(s): I suggest 7 well Flower Palettes at $4.52 apiece. I suggest an order of 2 from Dick Blick online. There are others you might want in addition.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;Small round or square white china plate for dry brush painting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;“Pentel Clic” white eraser housed in plastic pen like housing. Available at Office Stores.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;Small grey kneaded eraser&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;Scotch removable tape on Blue plaid card also available at Office Stores&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;An eye dropper&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;Pencil sharpener electric available in class. Bring handheld as they are easier on pencils&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;Small pack or box of KLEENEX or Viva paper towels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

  &lt;li&gt;12” ruler&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Materials provided to you&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One portfolio with watercolor information and exercises (watercolor exercise paper provided)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Col-Erase 20044 Blue pencil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Foam board easel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Suggested Books (Helpful to read prior to class):&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;“Mixing Greens” by Michael Wilcox&lt;br /&gt;
“Color Mixing Swatch Book” also by Michael Wilcox&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Art Supply locations and links online:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Blick, Salt Lake City&lt;br /&gt;
1025 East 2100 South&lt;br /&gt;
(801) 832-0400&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;www.utrechtart.com&quot;&gt;www.utrechtart.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Dick Blick Art&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.dickblick.com&quot;&gt;www.dickblick.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Other Online Art Supply Stores:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Daniel Smith&lt;br /&gt;
1 (800) 426-6740&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;www.danielsmith.com&quot;&gt;www.danielsmith.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Cheap Joe’s Art Stuff&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;1(800) 227-2788&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;www.cheapjoes.com&quot;&gt;www.cheapjoes.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Jerry’s Artarama Art Supplies&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;1(800) 827-8478&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;www.jerrysartarama.com&quot;&gt;www.jerrysartarama.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center bold&quot;&gt;Questions? Email Elaine at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:ehult@cox.net&quot;&gt;ehult@cox.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">NOTE: NO CLASS APRIL 14</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Botanical Composition &amp;amp; Style</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/botanical-composition/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Botanical Composition &amp;amp; Style" /><published>2017-04-10T20:04:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T20:58:50-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/botanical-composition</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/botanical-composition/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong class=&quot;green&quot;&gt;INSTRUCTOR:&lt;/strong&gt; Natalia Wilkins-Tyler&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong class=&quot;green&quot;&gt;LIMIT:&lt;/strong&gt; 15&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Imaginative, interesting and dynamic composition can transform a botanical painting or illustration into a masterpiece. It is through composition that you introduce your own personal style into your work. This class helps to explain the elements that go towards creating a good composition and the basic principles underlying a successful illustration. The class will work entirely in graphite pencil, but the principles presented apply to all art media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/refund-policy&quot;&gt;RED BUTTE GARDEN REFUND AND CANCELLATION POLICY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Materials List&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Graphite Pencils: 6H, 4H, 2H, HB, 2B, 2B, 4B,6B Brand of your choice. Tom Bow brand available only online&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pad of Drawing Paper 11x14 Strathmore recommended available at Blick,Sugarhouse and Michaels 300 series or 400 series.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pad of tracing paper 11x14 Canson Foundation series, Red White and Black cover and can only be purchased locally at Hobby Lobby for around $8. There is always a 40% discount offered  and can be accessed online at cashier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pad of Bristol paper 11x14 Strathmore or Canson, Vellum or plate surface finish, 300 or 400 series&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pentel white “Clic” eraser, refillable and available at all office supply stores&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A roll of “Scotch” brand “Removable” tape found in office supply stores on a blue plaid cardboard hanger hanging on a tape display&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A “kneaded” eraser It is gray and square shaped&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A hand held or battery operated pencil sharpener&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A roll of white “Artists’ Tape” available at Blick store in Sugarhouse&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A make-up or soft basring brush to sweep away eraser particles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Small tortillions-rolled paper smudge sticks also available at Blick store&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Materials Provided by Instructor&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 foam board easel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A set of view finders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A blue sketch pencil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wilkinsillustration.com/about&quot;&gt;Instructor's Bio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wilkinsillustration.com/&quot;&gt;Visit Natalia's Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;text-center bold&quot;&gt;Contact Information: 801-581-8454&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">INSTRUCTOR: Natalia Wilkins-Tyler
LIMIT: 15</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Updates from Around the Garden</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/updates-from-around-the-garden/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Updates from Around the Garden" /><published>2017-04-10T17:02:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T17:07:50-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/updates-from-around-the-garden</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/updates-from-around-the-garden/">&lt;p&gt;As the snow melts and the garden begins to bloom, life awakens at Red Butte. Our collections of conifers, roses, daffodils, and more are alive with the spirit of spring. The garden has never looked so good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As our garden changes colors and forms, so has our website. We at Red Butte have worked hard to create a refreshed and streamlined way for you to access our events and information. The new site brings a modern design, enhanced functionality, and a mobile optimized experience for visitors on the go. We hope you enjoy it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With warmer weather on our doorstep, it’s time to start planning for the 2017 Outdoor Concert Series. Tickets will be available for garden members online on Monday, April 24th at 7PM and in-person on Tuesday, April 25th. Tickets for the general public go on sale Monday, May 1st at 9AM both in-person and online. Renew or purchase a Garden-Plus Membership level or above by April 21st in order to participate in the April 24th member-only online presale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/concert-series.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Red Butte Garden Concert Series&quot; title=&quot;Red Butte Garden Concert Series&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; style=&quot;max-width:700px&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text-center italic&quot;&gt;For more information, &lt;a href=&quot;/concerts&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transform your garden by picking up some new plants at the annual Spring Plant Sale! The members-only day is May 12th while the general public day is May 13th. Here you will be able to purchase a range of indoor and outdoor plant species. Come check it out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/spring-plant-sale.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Red Butte Garden Spring Plant Sale&quot; title=&quot;Red Butte Garden Spring Plant Sale&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; style=&quot;max-width:700px&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text-center italic&quot;&gt;For more information, &lt;a href=&quot;/spring-plant-sale&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, the new Water Conservation Garden Grand Opening is May 20th. This inspiring new space will showcase the beauty and diversity of water-wise plants. Enjoy plants of all varieties, each with unique methods of conserving water and living in a desert ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/water-conservation-garden-opening.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Water Conservation Garden Grand Opening&quot; title=&quot;Water Conservation Garden Grand Opening&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; style=&quot;max-width:700px&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text-center italic&quot;&gt;For more information, &lt;a href=&quot;/water-conservation-garden-grand-opening&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your dedication and passion for the garden. All of us here are excited to introduce you and your family to the beauty of nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to make a donation to the garden:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://55218.blackbaudhosting.com/55218/Annual-Gift&quot;&gt;
  &lt;form method=&quot;POST&quot; action=&quot;https://55218.blackbaudhosting.com/55218/Annual-Gift&quot;&gt;
    &lt;input class=&quot;green-button&quot; type=&quot;button&quot; value=&quot;Make a Donation&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;/form&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll see you soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;br /&gt;
Red Butte Garden and Arboretum&lt;br /&gt;
300 Wakara Way, Salt Lake City,&lt;br /&gt;
Utah, 84108&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">As the snow melts and the garden begins to bloom, life awakens at Red Butte. Our collections of conifers, roses, daffodils, and more are alive with the spirit of spring. The garden has never looked so good!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">38th ANNUAL SPRING PLANT SALE</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/spring-plant-sale/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="38th ANNUAL SPRING PLANT SALE" /><published>2017-04-10T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T18:02:38-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/spring-plant-sale</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/spring-plant-sale/">&lt;p class=&quot;text-center red bold&quot;&gt;Please enter through the Amphitheatre gates. See map below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;It’s time once again to support the Garden at our annual benefit plant sale!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL FIND:&lt;/strong&gt; The Garden offers an impressive selection of herbs, specialty annuals, vegetables, sun and shade perennials, ornamental grasses, shrubs, conifers, roses, vines, trees, and the best selection of heirloom vegetables, native plants and water-wise plants! You'll find plants for every situation, including gifts and high-altitude gardening. Most of the plants are grown by local nurseries and many of the vegetables are grown here in our own greenhouses! This annual plant sale and fundraiser is always a great way to welcome the planting season!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;We also offer a variety of organic gardening products such as fertilizers, and coco-fiber that when mixed into your garden or container soil, aids with water retention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXPERTS ON HAND:&lt;/strong&gt; With our Garden staff and volunteers, there will be plenty of qualified help to answer your plant and gardening questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHERE:&lt;/strong&gt; The Red Butte Garden Amphitheatre. From the four-way stop sign at Chipeta and Wakara Way, turn left (or North) and follow the signs. Enter through the north-facing gate used for general admission during concerts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT TO BRING:&lt;/strong&gt; If you have your own small wagon, bring it! We have a few shopping carts and plenty of cardboard plant trays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARKING:&lt;/strong&gt; Parking is available in lot #75 outside the sale entrance and in lot #80 for overflow parking. To ease any inconvenience, Garden staff will operate a passenger shuttle from the sale entrance to overflow lots (see map) from 1pm Friday as long as needed. We also protect a “loading only” area near the sale entrance/checkout for loading plants after you are able to collect your vehicle. Note too that there are few handicapped parking stalls in this particular University lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Support the Garden and find some great plants! Plan ahead for Mother’s Day by purchasing a colorful hanging basket. See you at the sale!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/spring-plant-sale-parking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Red Butte Garden Spring Plant Sale Parking&quot; title=&quot;Red Butte Garden Spring Plant Sale Parking&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; style=&quot;max-width:700px;border: 1px solid black;&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/documents/spring-plant-sale-parking.pdf&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE for a larger map.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SECTION HIGHLIGHTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Our extensive vegetable selection this year includes over 180 different varieties. This includes 60 different tomato cultivars, 32 different peppers (sweet and hot), 21 pumpkins and squash and a wide range of greens. At least 95 different vegetables are heirlooms. We will offer both an heirloom and a hybrid selection for most of the vegetables available. Quite a few of the selections will have been trialed here at the Garden, so you can try the varieties our staff and volunteers have grown and recommended. We will also have a selection of smaller cultivars that are ideal for small spaces or container gardening.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Nothing beats the color of flowering annuals for the summer garden! We will have a variety of colors and textures, sun and shade annuals, as well as a wide variety of succulents. And, don’t forget a hanging basket or mixed planter as a great Mother’s Day gift!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Don’t forget your favorite culinary, medicinal, tea, and fragrance herbs! Great fresh or preserved, we have a wide variety to grow and enjoy at home. Check out the slow-to-bolt Cilantro ‘Ole’ or the cold hardy Rosemary ‘Gorizia’. Get them and your favorite Lavender varieties before they’re gone! This year we’ll have several new varieties of Basil; like ‘Balsamic Blooms’ with gorgeous ornamental flowers! Try combinations like Chamomile, Lemon Grass and Mint in a container to stock up your tea cabinet. Save money on your grocery bill and have fun!!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;We will have over 300 different species and cultivars of perennials, including sun loving, and shade loving. There is definitely something for every type of situation, including high elevation gardens. Check out the ‘Specialty Perennial’ section if you’re looking for something truly unique, and allow yourself plenty of time to browse!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Ornamental grasses add texture and movement to your garden! Often overlooked, grasses serve many functions in a garden in addition to aesthetics. Ornamental Grasses can be used as a focal point or in mass, and come in a variety of colors, textures, sizes, bloom times, and water requirements. Come choose from Bluestem, Feather Reed, Sea Oats, Silver Grass, Muhly, Moor grass and more, including selections ideal for shadier areas, such as Japanese Forest Grass and Sedges. No matter the site conditions or your personal taste we are sure to have an ornamental grass for you!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Groundcovers can solve many garden problems, such as steep slopes and masking tough areas with texture and color. From vigorous foliage cover like Wintercreeper and Pachysandra, to delicate flowering swathes of Blue Lithodora or Delosperma, we have a groundcover for every growing condition. Don’t forget about the eye-catching Plumbago for three-season interest!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Our selection of roses includes old-fashioned garden roses, modern shrub roses, miniatures and climbers. Beautiful blooms of all colors, combined with winter hardiness and disease-resistance, make lovely additions in the home landscape. All our roses are ‘own-root’, not grafted, which means although they may be small at first, your favorite rose will not revert back to a root stock variety after a harsh winter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;We offer a wide variety of flowering and shade trees, unique conifers, colorful shrubs and flowering vines. We also offer a variety of fruit trees, berry bushes, strawberries and rhubarb. Come with your questions and site information and let us help you select the right plant for your situation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/documents/planting-landscaping-trees.pdf&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt; for information on how to properly plant a tree, and register your new tree on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.slco.org/milliontrees/&quot;&gt;http://www.slco.org/milliontrees/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Deciphering our plant ID cards:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An outline of the state of Utah means its native. Be aware that not all natives prefer low-water, Utah has many natives that require regular irrigation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An orange sticker with a bee means the plant is bee friendly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A green sticker with a mountain means the plant is hardy at high elevations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be sure to check water requirements listed on the ID cards, whether by text or sticker.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Shop TWICE! Once to grab those important not-to-miss plants, and a second time to browse for overlooked treasures. And don’t forget that perfect Mother’s day gift!&lt;/h5&gt;</content><summary type="html">Please enter through the Amphitheatre gates. See map below.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TRES FROMME LECTURE</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/design-vision-lecture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TRES FROMME LECTURE" /><published>2017-04-10T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T19:48:02-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/design-vision-lecture</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/design-vision-lecture/">&lt;p class=&quot;text-center red bold&quot;&gt;REGISTRATION REQUIRED&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;As part of the Water Conservation Garden Grand Opening events, join us at this lecture featuring the main designer of the Water Conservation Garden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Fromme's design’s work focuses on intensely organization and site-specific public space and garden collaborations throughout the country. He brings a vast knowledge of horticulture, garden precedents, aesthetics, and design to each project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/water-conservation-garden-grand-opening&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE for more information about the May 20 Water Conservation Garden Grand Opening&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;tan-bg&quot;&gt;

  &lt;br /&gt;
  &lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;TRES FROMME BIO&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Tres Fromme is known for his expertise with facilitating team-based creative group process and input to create compelling and memorable places that invest participants in the outcomes. His designs all creatively innovate within the traditions and diverse contexts of the project. A proponent of experiential design, he choreographs relationships among people, spaces, and plants. For a decade Fromme led planning and design at Longwood Gardens in Kennett Square, Pennsylvania and recently for four years at the Atlanta Botanical Garden.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Education:&lt;/h5&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;University of Georgia, Master of Landscape Architecture, 1996&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;University of Delaware, Honors Bachelor of Plant Science; concentration in Ornamental Horticulture Summa Cum Laude, 1993&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;br /&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row-fluid&quot;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-6&quot;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/tres-fromme-by-chris-kozarich.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tres Fromme by Chris Kozarich&quot; title=&quot;Tres Fromme by Chris Kozarich&quot; class=&quot;responsive img-center&quot; style=&quot;max-width:400px;&quot; /&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-6&quot;&gt;

    &lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Selected Public Garden Projects&lt;/h4&gt;

    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Atlanta Botanical Garden Edible Garden; Garden Lights/Holiday Nights&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Atlanta Botanical Garden Gainesville/Smithgall Woodland Gardens&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Bok Tower Gardens Master Plan&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Carleen Bright Arboretum Master Plan&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cape Fear Botanical Garden Master Plan&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Desert Botanical Garden Desert Terraces and Portal&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Huntsville Botanical Garden Core Master Plan&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Longwood Gardens East Conservatory and Indoor Children’s Garden&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Tulsa Botanic Garden Children’s Discovery Garden and Floral Terraces&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</content><summary type="html">REGISTRATION REQUIRED</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">CERTIFICATE OF WESTERN HORTICULTURE OPEN HOUSE</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/western-horticulture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="CERTIFICATE OF WESTERN HORTICULTURE OPEN HOUSE" /><published>2017-04-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-09T12:44:03-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/western-horticulture</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/western-horticulture/">&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Red Butte Garden and Lifelong Learning invite you to a special open house on Earth Day, Saturday April 22.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Come learn more about the Certificate of Western Horticulture, a certificate designed to help Wasatch Front gardeners learn techniques to become more successful gardeners. Enjoy a tour of Red Butte Garden, meet fellow gardeners, instructors, and friends. Beverages and bagels provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center red bold&quot;&gt;REGISTRATION REQIRED&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Red Butte Garden and Lifelong Learning invite you to a special open house on Earth Day, Saturday April 22.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GARDEN POETRY READING</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/poetry-reading/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GARDEN POETRY READING" /><published>2017-04-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-09T12:29:14-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/poetry-reading</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/poetry-reading/">&lt;p&gt;Celebrate spring and go on a walk through the Garden with the winners of our spring poetry contest! Throughout the month of April the Garden is hosting 11 poetry boxes, showcasing works from local poets in honor of National Poetry Month. Stroll the Garden with the poets to hear live readings and gain details about the meaning behind their words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Authors in attendance will include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Megan Olsen&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maya Johnson&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Melinda Birrell&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sara Bybee&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Tina Thomas&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Pam Tucker&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Joyce Marder&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Christina Elizabeth&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Carol Anderson&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Julie Chytraus&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Acacia Ott&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;REGISTRATION REQUIRED&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
	&lt;p class=&quot;red&quot;&gt;SOLD OUT! Click Below To Be Added to Waiting List&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;https://redbuttegarden.formstack.com/forms/poetry_walk_waitlist&quot;&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; name=&quot;Apply-Button&quot; value=&quot;Waiting List&quot; class=&quot;apply-button hover&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;</content><summary type="html">Celebrate spring and go on a walk through the Garden with the winners of our spring poetry contest! Throughout the month of April the Garden is hosting 11 poetry boxes, showcasing works from local poets in honor of National Poetry Month. Stroll the Garden with the poets to hear live readings and gain details about the meaning behind their words.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ARBOR DAY</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/arbor-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ARBOR DAY" /><published>2017-04-07T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-09T12:29:14-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/arbor-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/arbor-day/">&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;There’s no better place than Red Butte Garden to celebrate Arbor Day! As Utah’s very own arboretum, we can't wait to share the wonderful world of trees. Due to the generous support of Rocky Mountain Power, join us for a fun day of activities and leave with a free tree to take home (while supplies last).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Thanks to funding in part by &lt;strong&gt;Salt Lake County Zoo, Arts, and Parks Program (ZAP)&lt;/strong&gt; Arbor Day is a ZAP Free Day! Everyone enjoys free Garden admission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Schedule of Events&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tree Giveaway&lt;/strong&gt; - Children’s Garden, All Day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Thanks to the generous support of &lt;storng&gt;Rocky Mountain Power&lt;/storng&gt;, all guests leave with a free White Fir, Abies concolor, to take home. Trees available while supplies last!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tree Scavenger Hunt&lt;/strong&gt; - Throughout the Garden, All Day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Red Butte Garden has an amazing collection of trees! See if you can find the ten trees we’ve highlighted for your Arbor Day visit as you explore the Garden today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploration Stops&lt;/strong&gt; - Throughout the Garden, All Day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Discover the amazing world of trees as you stroll through the Garden! Using your senses, discover the vital role leaves, trunks, roots, and seeds play in the life of a tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;American Conifer Society Booth&lt;/strong&gt; - Courtyard Garden, 9AM-Noon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Curious about conifers? Stop by the courtyard to meet David Olszyk of the American Conifer Society (ACS) and become an ACS member! Membership grants you exclusive access to ConiferQuarterly and all the latest conifer news.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poster Contest Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt; - Orangerie, 10-10:45AM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Students across the state have been busy learning about trees and creating their own posters to illustrate this year’s theme, &quot;Trees are Terrific Storytellers of the Past!” Help us recognize this year’s contest winners at the official Utah State Arbor Day Ceremony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tree Planting&lt;/strong&gt; - Rose Garden, 10:45-11:00AM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Participate in our 2017 Arbor Day tree planting! A new tree will be added to the Garden’s collection to commemorate this important holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Diversity of Deciduous Trees&lt;/strong&gt; - Courtyard Garden, April 28 from 11:30AM-12:30PM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Stop by for a lunchtime tour with Crystal Kim, Garden Horticulturist, to explore deciduous trees in the Garden. Discover unique trees that are good candidates for your own yard and how they can lower your energy bill year round. Bring your questions and leave with a free tree to take home due to the generous support of Rocky Mountain Power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center italic&quot;&gt;Tour meets in the Courtyard Garden. Space limited to 20 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://55218.blackbaudhosting.com/55218/The-Diversity-of-Deciduous-Trees&quot;&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; name=&quot;Apply-Button&quot; value=&quot;Register Now&quot; class=&quot;apply-button hover&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;hr width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incredible Conifers!&lt;/strong&gt; - Courtyard Garden, April 28 from 1-2PM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join David Olszyk of the American Conifer Society and members of the Garden’s conifer planning committee on a tour to discuss the Garden’s amazing collection and how conifers can add interest to your winter landscape. Bring your conifer-related questions and leave with a free tree to take home due to the generous support of Rocky Mountain Power.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;italic text-center&quot;&gt;Tour meets in the Courtyard Garden. Space limited to 20 guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://55218.blackbaudhosting.com/55218/Incredible-Conifersrock&quot;&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; name=&quot;Apply-Button&quot; value=&quot;Register Now&quot; class=&quot;apply-button hover&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;center&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/rocky-mountain-power.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Red Butte Garden thanks Rocky Mountain Power for it's generous support!&quot; title=&quot;Red Butte Garden thanks Rocky Mountain Power for it's generous support!&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; style=&quot;max-width:200px;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;</content><summary type="html">There’s no better place than Red Butte Garden to celebrate Arbor Day! As Utah’s very own arboretum, we can't wait to share the wonderful world of trees. Due to the generous support of Rocky Mountain Power, join us for a fun day of activities and leave with a free tree to take home (while supplies last).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GARDEN POETRY WALK</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/garden-poetry-walk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GARDEN POETRY WALK" /><published>2017-04-02T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-09T12:44:03-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/garden-poetry-walk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/garden-poetry-walk/">&lt;p&gt;Did you know April is National Poetry Month? Celebrate this important literary art with a stroll through the Garden to find eleven poetry boxes featuring poems written by winners of our Spring Poetry Contest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throughout April the Garden also hosts a special audio tour featuring recordings of our contest winners performing readings of their poems, all accessible from your cell phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow the instructions at each poetry box to access audio recordings. The audio tour is free, but normal cell phone carrier usage rates apply. Please be considerate of other Garden guests and listen to audio content through headphones or your phone’s earpiece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sign up to attend a Garden Poetry Reading featuring live readings from many of the poets themselves on Wednesday, April 26 from 5:30-6:30PM. &lt;a href=&quot;/poetry-reading&quot;&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;/images/misc/garden-poetry-walk.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/garden-poetry-walk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garden Poetry Walk Locations&quot; title=&quot;Garden Poetry Walk Locations&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row-fluid&quot;&gt;

	&lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-8&quot;&gt;
		&lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Special thanks to our Garden Poetry Walk sponsors:&lt;/h4&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-4&quot;&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/images/misc/poetry-sponsors.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Poetry Sponsors&quot; title=&quot;Poetry Sponsors&quot; class=&quot;responsive&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</content><summary type="html">Did you know April is National Poetry Month? Celebrate this important literary art with a stroll through the Garden to find eleven poetry boxes featuring poems written by winners of our Spring Poetry Contest.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WATER CONSERVATION GARDEN GRAND OPENING</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/water-conservation-garden-grand-opening/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WATER CONSERVATION GARDEN GRAND OPENING" /><published>2017-04-01T18:22:00-06:00</published><updated>2017-04-10T19:23:42-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/water-conservation-garden-grand-opening</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/water-conservation-garden-grand-opening/">&lt;p class=&quot;bold text-center green&quot;&gt;Open from 9AM-9PM - Free admission for children ages 17 and under thanks to a generous donation from Sandi Behnken&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center bold&quot;&gt;Guided garden tours will be available throughout the day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;The Water Conservation Garden has been designed to demonstrate that beautiful gardens need not require heavy application of water. Our intent is to present a garden so attractive that home and business owners will want to garden and landscape in this way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;This garden will bring an end to the myth that water-wise gardening can only exist in a landscape of rock and cacti. With the addition of this three-acre garden, Red Butte Garden will also add new educational programs to teach people how to create their own water-wise landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;Like all our gardens, the Water Conservation Garden will evolve and change over time as young plants mature and more water-wise plants become available in the trade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;h4 class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;SCHEDULED EVENTS&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row-fluid&quot;&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-4&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;10AM - 3PM&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Drop in and enjoy water-wise kids crafts in Em's Sprout House in the Children's Garden&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Explore Botany Bin Education Stations throughout the Water Conservation Garden&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Discover Welcome Stations at each new themed area of the new garden&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-4&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;Noon - 1PM&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rain Dance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    performance by the &lt;em&gt;Wasatch Eagle Dancers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;div class=&quot;col-sm-4&quot;&gt;
  &lt;h5 class=&quot;text-center green&quot;&gt;7 - 8PM&lt;/h5&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water Conservation Garden Design &amp;amp; Vision Lecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
    Creativity Run Dry: Designing the Red Butte Garden Water Conservation Garden&lt;br /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;Presented by Garden Designer Tres Fromme, Principal, 3.Fromme Design&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class=&quot;text-center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/design-vision-lecture&quot;&gt;For more information and to register to attend this lecture please CLICK HERE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;</content><summary type="html">Open from 9AM-9PM - Free admission for children ages 17 and under thanks to a generous donation from Sandi Behnken</summary></entry></feed>
